谢谢Raido  有了这种概念之后  让我们
Thanks Raido, with that in mind let's add
在我们的应用上添加一个刷新菜单按钮
a Refresh Menu button to our app. For temporary
这只是暂时的  否则Raido会和我们生气的
purposes only though, otherwise Raido would be mad at
在Android上  菜单的选项是定义在XML文件里面的
us. On Android, menu options are defined in XML
而且它们可以被Fragment或者Activity使用
and they can be declared for fragments or
当Fragment或者Activity创建的时候  它们会
activities. When the fragment or activity is created, it
将XML文件扩展成应用中真正的菜单选项
inflates this XML into the actual menu items in
你会看到这里有操作按钮  也就是菜单选项
the app. You'll see that there are Action buttons
并且它们显示在ActionBar（控制栏）中
which are menu items that appear in the Action bar,
比如这个搜索菜单项  这个地方是保留给
such as this Search Menu item. This space is reserved
你的应用中最重要的操作的  然后其余不是很重要的菜单项
for the most prominent actions in your app. Then anything
将会放入更多菜单里
else that's less important falls into the overflow menu by
通过单击这个三个点的按钮你就能看到它们
tapping on this button with the three dots. These menu
这些菜单项是按照最常用到最不常用的方式来排序的
items are ordered from most frequently used to least frequently
在拥有更多屏幕显示区域的大屏设备上
used. And on larger devices that have more screen real
你可以指定在ActionBar还有足够空间的情况下
estate, you can specify that some of these menu items can
让这些菜单显示在ActionBar上
actually go into the Action bar if there's room. If
如果你回过来看下我们项目的叫做res的
you go back to our project in the Resources folder
资源文件夹  这里有一个菜单文件夹
which is called res, there is a Menu folder and
在里面有一个main.xml的文件  如果你打开这个文件
inside that there's a main.xml file. If you open that up
你可以看到菜单的XML布局文档  这其中
you see the menu layout XML, and that there's a
只定义了一个设置菜单选项  它不会在
single menu option defined for Settings. It will never show up
ActionBar里面作为一个操作项来显示  也就是说
as an action in the Action bar, meaning that it
它会被放入更多菜单里  你可以通过在手机上查看你的应用
will be in the Overflow menu. You can verify this by
来确定这一点  为了定义菜单项的顺序
checking the app on your phone. To define the ordering
你可以加入多个菜单选项到这个XML文件里面
of menu items, you can just add multiple items to this
然后它们会按照定义的顺序显示在你的应用里面
XML file, and then they will show up in that order
如果你不喜欢这种顺序  而
in the app. If you don't like the order though, and
你想要明确地设置它们  你可以指定
you want to explicitly set it, then you can specify
orderInCategory属性的值  目前的数值设置的是100
this orderInCategory value. Right now it's set as 100,
所以设置选项就会出现在所有的
so that the Settings menu will be at the bottom of
我们在应用中定义的其他菜单项的最下面
all the other menu options that we define in our app.
唯一应该出现在设置菜单的下面的
The only Menu option that should show up below the Settings
就是帮助菜单  请点击这个链接来了解更多的细节
menu is the Help menu. Check out the link for more details.